http://kuryakyn.com/privacy-notice

Live Help Software
Search
MY CART (0)
Products +
Accessories
AudioLightingAccessory MountsHandlebar Controls, Grips & MirrorsPegs & Foot ControlsCovers, Trims & AccentsPerformance Touring & ComfortWindshields & Air ManagementLuggage, Organizers and Storage CoversThe Shop
News +
Events
Blog
Event Schedule
Connect
With Us
About Us
Contact Us
This Privacy Notice
(the "Privacy Notice") describes how the Motorsport Aftermarket Group
and our associated entities collect, use, and share your information. Along
with the Motorsport Aftermarket Group, this Privacy Notice applies to J&P
Cycles, Motorcycle Superstore, Answer Racing, Biker's Choice, BikeMaster, Black
Brand, Bully Locks, Burly Brand, First Gear, DragonFire Racing, Kuryakyn, MS
Racing, Mustang Motorcycle Seats, Performance Machine, Powersports U,
Progressive Suspension, ProTaper, Quad Boss, Roland Sands Design,
SkidLid Helmets, SS Gear, Twin Power, Vance & Hines, Xtreme Machines,
Crusher Performance, Motorcycle USA, and MagNetForceDirect
(collectively, the "The Companies" or "we", "our," or "us").
This Privacy Notice
applies to your use of The Companies' websites, our mobile applications, and
all other digital and online services provided by The Companies (collectively,
the "Services") and describes our privacy practices relating to the
Services. It does not apply to information collected by
The Companies
offline, or to third party websites, applications, or services (including any
other affiliates' or organizations not named above).
1. Contact Information and Data Protection Officer
Motorsport Aftermarket Group
17771 Mitchell
North Irvine
California 92614
United States
949-440-5500
If you have any comments or questions about how we
collect and use your personal data
, communications can be directed to our postal
address, via email to
privacy@maggroup.com
or by telephone to 949-440-5500.
European Union or EEA Member States
We have appointed a
Data Protection Officer who is responsible for overseeing questions about this
privacy notice. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including
any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact our Data Protection
Officer using the details set out below.
Data Protection Officer
Email: dpo@maggroup.com
Phone: 949-440-5500
2. Applicability & Eligibility
We need to process your personal
data to operate our organization and provide you with certain Services. Before
accessing, using, or interacting with the Services you should carefully review
the terms and conditions of this Privacy Notice. Your use of the Services is
further governed by our Terms of Service,
which is also incorporated into your agreement with The Companies by this
reference.
By accepting our Privacy
Notice and Terms of Service, you are confirming that you have read and understood
these policies, including how and why we use your information. If you don't want
us to collect or process your personal data in the ways described in this Privacy
Notice, you should not use the Services. Please note we are not responsible for
the content or the privacy policies or practices of any third party
organization or service.
The Services are not directed
to children under the age of 16. You may not use the Services if you are under
the age of 16. If you are under the age of 18, you should not provide any
information on our Services.
3. Information Collection, Use & Sharing
The Companies
collect information about you and your
use of the Services through various means, including when you provide
information to us and when we automatically collect information about you when
you access, use, or interact with the Services.
Such processing is performed to provide
you with the Services. In some instances, you may be able to choose what
information to provide, but sometimes we require certain information for you to
use and for us to provide you the Services.
We rely on a number of legal bases to process the information
we receive about you from your use of the Services, including where: (1) you
have consented to the processing; (2) the processing is necessary to perform
the contractual obligations in order to provide the Services to you, including
those of our Terms of Use; (3) necessary to comply with a legal obligation, a
court order, or to exercise or defend legal claims; (4) necessary to protect
your vital interests, or those of others; (5) necessary in the public interest;
(6) necessary for the purposes of our or a third party's legitimate interests,
such as those of visitors, users, or partners; and (7) you have expressly made
the information public.
Where we process your information on the basis of consent, we
will clearly obtain your opt-in consent. Where given, you may withdraw your
consent at any time by contacting us at
privacy@maggroup.com
(or to dpo@maggroup.com
if you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States).
Where we process your information on the basis of
legitimate interests, we do so where the processing is necessary for your
legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party, unless there
is a good reason to protect your personal data which overrides those legitimate
interests.
The types of information The Companies may collect about you include:
3.1 Information You Provide To Us:
We generally process information you provide to us on the legal basis of
The Companies' legitimate interests in performing the function or
service you requested. Where appropriate, we may rely on alternate legal bases,
such as your consent to certain types of processing.
Account Information:
Certain Services users may register for an account (a
"Services Account"). We do not require you to register to use our Services.
However if you do register a Services Account, you will gain access to those areas
and features of the Services that require registration. The Companies
will collect certain information about you in connection with your registration
for a Services Account, which may include personal data and other information
such as a username and password.
Payment Transaction Information:
We may collect and store
information related to purchases of the Services. You may be required to provide
certain information to complete payments via the Services, including your
credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing
address (collectively, "Payment Information"), along with your name and
billing, delivery and shipping address, to complete payment transactions
through certain services. The Companies store your encrypted Payment
Information in compliance with the industry standards.
Please note The Companies
work with Service Providers (as defined below) to handle payment transactions. You
are subject to the Privacy Policies and Terms and Conditions of our Service
Providers when utilizing a third party service through The Companies' Services.
Please review the Service Providers' Privacy Policies and Terms and Conditions
before using their services.
Correspondence Information:
If you sign up, email us, subscribe to our blog, newsletters, sweepstakes,
or mailing lists, we may keep your message, email address, and
contact information to respond to your requests, provide the requested products
or Services, and to provide notifications or other correspondences to you.
If you do not want to receive
communications from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an
e-mail requesting the same to
privacy@maggroup.com
(or to dpo@maggroup.com
if you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States)
or by following the unsubscribe instructions found in any e-mail we send.
If you supply us with your
postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on
new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive
such mailings, please let us know by contacting us at
privacy@maggroup.com
(or to dpo@maggroup.com
if you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States)
or by calling our phone number provided above.
Please note
requests to remove your email address from our lists may take some time to fulfill.
We may also still contact you as needed to provide important announcements or
notifications regarding the Services.
Sponsorship Information:
Users may have the option to fill out an application for sponsorship via the Services, thus,
we may collect your personal data such as your first and last name, email,
phone number, address, resume, and age to assist with sponsorship requests.
Clip-on Recall Registration:
We collect personal data from you when you request
information from The Companies or register your clip-ons for recall via the
Services. We use this information in order to communicate with you regarding
your clip-on, to communicate with you regarding your inquiry, and respond to
your questions.
Promotions & Sweepstakes Information:
If you register for our promotions or sweepstakes, The Companies and our partners may
send you emails or other correspondence regarding the contest for which you registered,
and other contests, promotions, and sweepstakes.
Support Information:
You may provide information to us via a support
request submitted through the Services. We will use this information to assist
you with your support request and may maintain this information to assist you
or other users with support requests. Please do not submit any information to
us via a support submission, including confidential or sensitive information
that you do not wish for The Companies
or our Service Providers to have access to
or use in the future.
Form Information:
We may use forms to request certain information from
you on the Services, such as your contact information to assist with contacts
or service requests. This information may include personal data.
3.2 Information We Collect Automatically:
We use automatic
data collection and analytics technologies to collect aggregate and user-specific
information about your equipment, domain name, patterns of use, communication
data and the resources that you access and use on the Services, including your IP
address, browsing and navigation patterns. This information is used to improve
our Services.
We generally process information collected automatically on the legal basis
of The Companies' legitimate interests in assessing the use of its
Services. Where appropriate, we may rely on alternate legal bases, such as your
consent to certain types of processing.
Information we collect automatically through your use of the Services includes:
Social Login Data:
Certain Services may
allow you to log in using social media accounts, such as those available via
Facebook, Twitter, and Google. For those Services users that choose social
login, The Companies may receive information from your social account which makes
it easier for you to create a Services Account or login, such as your email
address. We currently also collect first name, last name, and profile photos
for all social logins, as well as gender and birthdate from those using
Facebook as a social login. We use the information to help you connect and share
public content with your friends and followers, to register you for a Services
Account, and to contact you via our newsletters if you opt-in.
Cookies, Web Beacons, Links, And Other Tracking Technologies:
The Companies may keep track of how you use and interact with the Services
through the use of cookies, web beacons, links, and
other tracking technologies. We do this to help analyze the use of and improve
the Services. Through these technologies we may automatically collect
information about your use of the Services and other online activities,
including our email correspondences, third-party services, and client
applications, and certain online activities after you leave the Services.
Link information is generally only analyzed on an aggregate basis.
Some Services features may not function properly if you disable cookies. Such data may include
analytics information, sites visited before visiting the Services, browser
type, operating system, and tracking of your interactions with our content and
emails.
We partner with third parties to manage our advertising on other sites. Our
third-party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to
provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.
IP Addresses:
We automatically collect the IP addresses of users of certain Services, such as website visitors, those
that log in to the Services, and those who post messages to the communities and
forums. We process this information on the basis of our legitimate interests in protecting
the Services and providing the Services to you.
Advertising Information:
We partner with third parties to manage our
advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use cookies or similar
technologies in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing
activities and interests. If you have chosen to connect your account to an
external third-party application, such as Facebook, or an app developed using
the API, you can change your settings and remove permission for the app by
changing your account settings.
Unique Identifiers:
When you use or access
the Services, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or
remotely store one or more "Unique Identifiers," such as a universally unique
identifier ("UUID"). A Unique Identifier may remain on your device
persistently, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the
Services. Some features of the Services may not function properly if use or
availability of Unique Identifiers is impaired or disabled.
Analytics Information:
We use data analytics to
ensure site functionality and improve the Services. We use analytics software
to allow us to understand the functionality of the Services on your phone. This
software may record information such as how often you use the Services, what
happens within the Services, aggregated usage, performance data, app errors and
debugging information, and where the Services were downloaded from. We do not link
the information we store within the analytics software to any personally
identifiable information that you submit within the mobile application.
Log File Information:
When you use our
Services, we may receive log file information such as your IP address, browser
type, access times, domain names operating system, the referring web page(s),
pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including
device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information.
We receive log file data when you interact with our Services,
for example, when you visit our website, sign into our Services, or interact
with our email notifications. The Companies uses log file data to provide,
understand, and improve our Services, and to customize the content we show you.
The Companies may link this log file to other information The Companies
collects about you via the Services.
Public Information:
The Companies may also collect
information about you from publicly available sources. Information you make
publicly available in any public or open forum, such as on a social network,
may be considered public information for the purposes of this Privacy Notice,
and may be accessed and collected by The Companies. Please be aware that any
content or information you share with or provide to third parties using or
related to your use of the Services are neither private, nor confidential.
The Companies is not responsible for any content or information you post or share with third
parties. If you do not wish for certain information to be public, please do not
share it publicly.
3.3 Information Use
The Companies uses the information we receive about you for the purposes described in this
Privacy Notice. We generally process personal data received about you
through our Services on the legal basis of The Companies' legitimate
interests in providing the Services and their functionality to you where such processing is
necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by The Companies
or by our Service Providers related to the Services.
Where appropriate, we may rely on alternate legal bases, such as your consent to
certain types of processing.
The Companies will generally use
your information in the following circumstances on the legal basis of
legitimate interests to provide the Services requested:
Providing and Improving Our Services:
We may use your information to improve and customize our Services, including
sharing of your information for such purposes, and we do so as it is necessary
to pursue our legitimate interests of improving our Services for our users. This
is also necessary to enable us to pursue our legitimate interests in
understanding how our Services are being used, and to explore and unlock ways
to develop and grow our business. It is also necessary to allow us to pursue
our legitimate interests in improving our Services, efficiency, interest in
Services for users and obtaining insights into usage patterns of our Services. We
use your information to provide and improve the Services and our products, to
provide and service Services Accounts, for billing and payments, for
identification and authentication, for targeted online and offline marketing
including through tools like Facebook Custom Audience and Google Customer
Match, to contact users or interested parties, and for general research and
aggregate reporting.
Keeping Our Services Safe And Secure:
We may also use your information for safety and
security purposes, including sharing of your information for such purposes, and
we do so because it is necessary to pursue our legitimate interests in ensuring
the security of our Services, including enhancing protection of our community
against spam, harassment, intellectual property infringement, crime, and
security risks of all kind.
Third-Party Advertisements:
The Companies may utilize the services of third-party advertising companies,
including Google and others, to serve ads to you when you use our Services or
other sites across the Internet, or to perform remarketing services. These
third parties may collect information about your visits to certain pages of our
Services and may use technology like cookies to store information about your
use of the Services. The information collected may be reported back to us, and
we may link this information to personal data we have collected about you. This
information allows us to track which other websites have linked visitors to our
Services, what pages of our Services are used by and are of interest to
visitors, so we may provide better, more targeted advertising regarding our
business and Services. More information about interest-based advertising and
similar practices may be available at
http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp
3.4 Information Sharing
When you access or use the Services, we collect, use, share,
and otherwise process your personal data as described in this Privacy Notice.
European Union or EEA Member States
If you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States,
The Companies will not share, sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your personal
data to third parties without your express consent.
Outside of the European Union or EEA Member States
The Companies will not share, sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your
private personal data to third parties without your consent or another valid
legal basis permitted by law. The Companies will share your information in the
following circumstances on the legal basis of the legitimate interests of
providing the requested Services:
Within The Companies:
We may share and process information internally within The Companies and with our subsidiaries
and affiliates. The Companies' personnel may have access to your information as
needed to provide and operate the Services in the normal course of business. This
includes information regarding your
use and interaction with the Services.
Affiliated Businesses:
The Companies is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them for a
variety of purposes, including assisting us to perform and improve the
Services. These businesses may sell items or services to you through the
Services or, with your consent, offer promotions (including email promotions)
to you. The Companies may also provide services or sell products jointly with
affiliated businesses, including providing information to such partners to
allow them to more effectively market to you. When an affiliated business
assists in facilitating your transaction, we may need to share information
related to the transaction with that affiliated business in order to facilitate
your transaction, and this forms part of the Services we provide in accordance
with our Terms of Use. We rely on your consent (which can be withdrawn at any
time) to send marketing messages.
Service Providers:
The Companies work with various organizations and individuals to help provide the Services to
you ("Service Providers"), such as website and data hosting companies
and companies providing analytics information, like Google Analytics.
The Companies need to engage such third-party Service Providers to help us operate, provide,
and market the Services. These third parties have only limited access to your
information and may use your information only to perform these tasks on our
behalf. Information we share to our Service Providers may include both
information you provide to us and information we collect about you, including personal
data and information from data collection tools like cookies, web beacons, and
log files.
The Companies take reasonable steps to ensure
that our Service Providers are obligated to reasonably protect your information on
The Companies' behalf. If The Companies
become aware that a Service Provider is using or
disclosing information improperly, we will take commercially reasonable steps
to end or correct such improper use or disclosure.
We share personal data with our Service Providers on the legal basis of
The Companies' legitimate interests in providing you with the Services.
Our engagement of Service Providers is often necessary
for us to provide the Services to you, particularly where such companies play
important roles like helping us keep our Services operating and secure. In some
other cases, these service providers aren't strictly necessary for us to
provide the Services, but help us make it better, like by helping us conduct
research into how we could better serve our users. In these latter cases, we
have a legitimate interest in working with service providers to make our
Services better.
Third Party Technologies:
Third-party plug-ins also may collect information about your use of the Services. For
example, when you load a page on The Companies that has a social plug-in from a
third-party site or service, such as a "Like" or "Send" button, you are also
loading content from that third-party site. That site may request cookies
directly from your browser. These interactions are subject to the privacy
policy of the third-party site. In addition, certain cookies and other similar
technologies on the Services are used by third parties for targeted online
marketing and other purposes. These technologies allow a partner to recognize
your computer or mobile device each time you use the Services. Please be aware
that when you use third-party sites or services, their own terms and privacy
policies will govern your use of those sites or services. The Companies chooses
and manages these third-party technologies placed on its Services. However,
these are third-party technologies, and they are subject to that third party's
privacy policy. We rely on your consent to drop and read non-technically
necessary cookies. The Companies are not responsible for the privacy or
security practices of third parties.
Business Transactions:
The Companies may purchase other businesses or their assets, sell our business assets, or be
involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets
(a "Business Transaction"). Your information, including personal data,
may be among assets sold or transferred as part of a Business Transaction. In
some cases, The Companies may choose to buy or sell assets. Such transactions
may be necessary and in our legitimate interests, particularly our interest in
making decisions that enable our organization to develop over the long term.
Safety and Lawful Requests:
We may be required to disclose Services user information pursuant to lawful requests,
such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We
generally do not disclose user information unless we have a good faith belief
that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets
applicable legal standards. We may share your information when we believe it is
necessary to comply with applicable laws, to protect our interests or property,
to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Services or
using The Companies name, or to protect the safety of any person. This
may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or
government agencies. Nothing in this Privacy
Notice is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have
to a third party's, including a government's, request to disclose your
information.
Aggregated Non-Personal Data :
We may disclose aggregated, non-personal data received from providing the Services, including
information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. The
Companies may share demographic information with business partners, but it will
be aggregated and de-personalized, so that personal data is not revealed.
4. Public Forums & Community
The Companies offer various
communities and forums across the Services. We offer several features that
allow users to connect and communicate in public or semi-public spaces as part
of these Services. You don't have to use these features, but if you do, please
use common sense and good judgment when posting in these community spaces or
sharing your personal data with others through the Services.
Please be aware that any personal
data that you choose to submit there can be read, collected, or used by others,
or could be used to send unsolicited messages to you. We may engage certain
third parties and Service Providers to assist in providing community services
to you and, in the context of that relationship, we need to share some of your
information with such third parties in order to provide that service. The
Companies generally does not control or remove content from public Services
spaces, and your posts may remain public after your account is closed. You are
responsible for the personal data that you choose to post in public Services
spaces
Please also note we may
automatically collect certain information about you when you browse or post to
the communities and forums, such as your computer's IP address or a device
identification number.
5. Your Rights & Choices Regarding Your Information
5.1 Your Rights
The Companies seek to ensure all individuals are provided with the
rights mandated by their governing jurisdiction. Not all of the rights discussed in this Privacy Notice
will apply to each individual data subject and may not apply to you depending
upon your jurisdiction.
You may benefit
from a number of rights in relation to your information that we process. Some
rights apply only in certain limited cases, depending on your location. If you
would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your personal data, you can do
so by contacting us. Upon request, The Companies will provide you with
information about whether we hold any of your personal data.   In certain
cases where we process your information, you may also have a right to restrict
or limit the ways in which we use your personal data. In certain circumstances,
you also have the right to request the deletion of your personal data, and to
obtain a copy of your personal data in an easily accessible format.
To the extent that
such rights are mandated by the laws applicable to the individual data subject,
such as all data subjects residing in the European
Union ("EU"), the following rights may apply: the right to access
(GDPR, Article 15); the right to rectification (GDPR, Article16); the right to
erasure (GDPR, Article 17); the right to restrict processing (GDPR, Articles
18); the right of object (GDPR, Article 21); and if applicable, the right to
data portability (GDPR, Article 20).
You may also have a right to lodge a complaint with an appropriate data privacy
regulatory authority (GDPR, Article 77).
If we process your
information based on our legitimate interests as explained in this Privacy
Notice, or in the public interest, you can object to this processing in certain
circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your information unless
we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is
needed for legal reasons. Where we use your data for direct marketing purposes,
you can always object using the unsubscribe link in such communications or
changing your account settings.
Where you have provided
consent to certain data processing, you have the right to withdraw that consent
at any time by contacting
privacy@maggroup.com
(or to dpo@maggroup.com
if you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States)
A withdrawal of consent will not affect the validity
of our use of your personal data up until the point you have withdrawn your
consent.
If you no longer wish to use
the Services or receive service-related messages (except for legally required
notices), then you may contact us using the information above.
5.2 Access To The Information The Companies Has Collected About You
The Companies provides certain tools and
settings within the Services to help you access, correct, delete, or modify your
personal data associated with the Services.  The Companies welcomes you to
contact us regarding the information we have collected about you, including
regarding the nature and accuracy of the data that has been collected about
you, to request an update, modification, or deletion of your information, to
opt-out of certain Services uses of your information, or to withdraw any
consent you may have granted to The Companies.
Please note requests to delete or remove your information
do not necessarily ensure complete or comprehensive
removal of the content or information posted, and removed
information may persist in backup copies indefinitely.
Please note that if you choose to delete your information or opt-out of the
collection and use of your information, you understand that certain features,
including but not limited to access to the Services, may no longer be available
to you.
5.3 Data Retention
The Companies will retain your information only for as long as is necessary for the
purposes set out in this Privacy Notice, for as long as an account is active,
as described in this Privacy Notice, or as needed to provide the Services to
you. The Companies will retain and use your information to the extent necessary
to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain
your information to comply with applicable tax/revenue laws), resolve disputes,
enforce our agreements, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Notice. In
addition, The Companies sellers may also be required to retain and use your
information in order to comply with certain legal obligations. We also retain
log files for internal analysis purposes. These log files are generally
retained for a brief period of time, except in cases where they are used for
site safety and security, to improve site functionality, or we are legally
obligated to retain them for longer time periods.
We may delete your personal data from our systems as part of a data
retention plan.
Following termination or deactivation of a Services Account, The Companies
may retain your information and content for a commercially reasonable time for
backup, archival, and audit purposes.
5.4 Opting-Out Of Communications From The Companies
Users
may opt-out of receiving certain communications from
The Companies
by sending us an
e-mail requesting the same to
privacy@maggroup.com
(or to dpo@maggroup.com
if you are located in the European Union or EEA Member States)
, following the unsubscribe process described in an email
communication, or by contacting us using the contact information provided above.
However, please note you may not opt-out of certain Services-related
communications, such as account verification, changes or updates to features of
the Services, or technical and security notices.
5.5 Do Not Track
The Companies do not currently employ a process for
automatically responding to "Do Not Track" (DNT) signals sent by web browsers,
mobile devices, or other mechanisms. Per industry standards, third parties may
be able to collect information, including personal data, about your online
activities over time and across different websites or online services when you
use Services. You may opt out of online behavioral ads at
http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
. You also may limit certain tracking by disabling cookies in your web browser.
6. Information Security
The
security of your personal data is important to us.
The Companies takes reasonable efforts to secure and protect the
privacy, accuracy, and reliability of your information and to protect it from
loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
The Companies
implements security measures as we deem appropriate and consistent with
industry standards. As no data security protocol is impenetrable,
The Companies
cannot guarantee the security of our systems or databases, nor can we guarantee
that personal data we collect about you will not be breached, intercepted,
destroyed, accessed, or otherwise disclosed without authorization. Accordingly,
any information you transfer to or from Services are provided at your own risk.
Please
do your part to help us keep your information secure. Services Account
information is protected by a password. It is important that you protect
against unauthorized access to your account and information by choosing your
password carefully and by keeping your password and computer secure, such as by
signing out after using the Services. You are responsible for maintaining the
confidentiality of your password and Services Account, and are fully
responsible for all activities that occur under your password or Services
Account.
The Companies
specifically reserves the right to terminate your
access to the Services and any contract you have with
The Companies
related to the Services in the event it learns or suspects you have disclosed
your Services Account or password information to an unauthorized third party.
7. Additional Provisions Regarding The Services & Your Information
7.1 Transfer And Storage Of Your Information
The United
States, European Economic Area ("EEA") Member States, and other
countries all have different laws relating to privacy and data protection. When
your information is moved from your home country to another country, the laws
and rules that protect your personal data in the country to which your
information is transferred may be different from those in the country in which
you live. For example, the circumstances in which law enforcement can access personal
data may vary from country to country. In particular, if your information is in
the United States, it may be accessed by government authorities in accordance
with U.S. law.
Please be
advised information
The Companies
collects about you via the Services may
be transferred, processed and/or accessed by us in the United States, or
another country where we, or our Service Providers operate.
Please be aware that the privacy laws and standards in
certain countries, including the rights of authorities to access your personal
data, may differ from those that apply in the country in which you reside.
If you are located outside the United States and
choose to allow us to collect information about you, please be aware that
The Companies
may transfer your personal data to the United States and process and store it
there.
We will transfer personal data
only to those countries to which we are permitted by law to transfer personal
data, and we will take steps to ensure that your personal data continues to
enjoy appropriate protections.
7.2 Processing Necessary For The Performance Of The Contract
You can choose whether or not
you want to use the Services. However, if you want to use the Services, you
need to agree to our Terms of Use, which set out the contract between The
Companies and the users of the Services. We cannot provide many of the Services
without your agreement to this contract, and without moving your personal data
to The Companies entities and Service Providers in various jurisdictions.
Therefore certain processing of your personal data is done on the legal basis
of processing necessary for the performance of the contract between you, as a
user of the Services, and The Companies.
7.3 Safely Using The Companies' Services
Despite The Companies'
safety and privacy controls, we cannot guarantee the Services are entirely free
of illegal, offensive, or otherwise inappropriate material, or that you will
not encounter inappropriate or illegal conduct from other users when using the Services.
You can help The Companies by notifying us of any unwelcome contact by
contacting us using the information below.
7.4 Your California Privacy Rights
Under California Civil Code Section
1798.83 (known as the "Shine the Light" law),
The Companies
Services users and customers
who are residents of California may request certain information about our
disclosure of personal data during the prior calendar year to third parties for
their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at
the address below or at
privacy@maggroup.com
with
"Request for California Privacy Information" on the
subject line and in the body of your message.
We will comply with your request
within thirty (30) days or as otherwise required by the statute. Please be
aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements
and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.
8. Changes to Our Privacy Notice
The Companies
may modify this Privacy Notice from time to time. The
most current version of this Privacy Notice will govern our use of your
information and will be located at /privacy-notice.
You may contact us to obtain prior versions. We will notify you of material
changes to this policy by posting a notice at the Services or by emailing you at
an email address associated with your Services Account, if applicable, and
provide an "at a glance" overview of any changes.
SHOP BY BIKE
My AccountMy Garage
LOOKING FOR ...
CatalogNew ProductsTop SellerBahnBlack by KuryakynISO®L.E.D.Passenger Comfort
SHOP BY CATEGORY
AudioLightingAccessory MountsHandlebar Controls, Grips & MirrorsPegs & Foot ControlsCovers, Trims & AccentsPerformance Touring & ComfortWindshields & Air ManagementLuggage, Organizers and Storage CoversThe Shop
ABOUT KURYAKYN
About UsCareersCustomer ServiceFAQFind a DealerLegal NoticeShipping MethodsTerms & ConditionsTerms of ServicePrivacy Notice
CONNECT WITH US
Contact UsE-NewsletterBlogVideosWallpapersEvents ScheduleFacebookTwitterYouTubeInstagram
WE’RE HERE TO HELP!
We are taking orders, shipping daily, and we are here to answer your questions.
For the health and safety of our employees, our sales & tech teams are working remotely.
We encourage the use of our
online chat portal
or via email, at info@kuryakyn.com
Thank you for your support during this exceptionally challenging time.
[CLOSE]
